ACTWU's Research Department Records 5619/016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Men's Clothing Negotiations - Wage Increase, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 33)
- ACWA - Retail Division, 1963-1978 (Box 71, Folder 34)
- ACW Strikes, Lockouts and Injunctions, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Organizing Activities Election: Laundries, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Organizing Activities Election: Outerwear & Sportswear, 1969-1975 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Organizing Activities Election: Retail, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Organizing Activities Elections: Other Industries, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Organizing Activities Elections Cleaning and Dyeing, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- ACW - Elections, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- ACW - Elections, 1970-1977 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Advance, 1964-1967 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Samuel J. Azzinaro, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Oma Barton, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Murray Finley, 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Sol Brandzel, 1971-1977 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Sol Brandzel, 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Richard Brazier, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- William DuChessi, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 17)
- Murray H. Finley, 1965-1967 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Murray H. Finley, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Murray H. Finley, 1973-1976 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Murray H. Finley, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 21)
- Sam Fox, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder 22)
- Charles Garrahan, 1971-1977 (Box 72, Folder 23)
- Sander Genis, 1955-1975 (Box 72, Folder 24)
- Harry Goldsmith, 1974-1975 (Box 72, Folder 25)
- Harry Lautman, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 26)
- Leonard Levy, 1973-1976 (Box 72, Folder 27)
- Leonard Levy, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 28)
- Joyce D. Miller, 1975-1977 (Box 72, Folder 29)
- Vera Miller, 1971-1977 (Box 72, Folder 30)
- Sam Nocella, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 31)
- Change in Leadership - May, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 32)
- Diana Nunes, 1972-1976 (Box 72, Folder 33)
- Jacob S. Potofsky, 1970-1976 (Box 72, Folder 34)
- Vincent Ricciardelli, 1975-1976 (Box 72, Folder 35)
- Joseph Salerno, 1971-1977 (Box 72, Folder 36)
- Howard D. Samuel, 1971-1975 (Box 72, Folder 37)
- Howard D. Samuel, 1975-1977 (Box 72, Folder 38)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 39)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 40)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1971-1975 (Box 72, Folder 41)
- Jack Sheinkman, 1975-1977 (Box 72, Folder 42)
- Louis Simon, 1963-1968 (Box 72, Folder 43)
- Louis Simon, 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 44)
- Louis Simon, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 45)
- Sol Stetin, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder 46)
- Val Wertheimer, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 47)
- ACW General, 1973-1976 (Box 72, Folder 48)
- ACWA General, 1969-1972 (Box 72, Folder 49)
- Arbitration Award, 1974-1976 (Box 72, Folder 50)
- Amalgamated Arbitration, Conciliation, Mediation, 1969-1974 (Box 72, Folder 51)
- Campus and Community Program, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 52)
- Contracts Signed: Bushelmen, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 53)
- Cotton garment Negotiations + Contract - June, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 54)
- ACWA Legislative Activities ACW Statements supporting or Opposing Legislation, 1975-1977 (Box 72, Folder 55)
- Amalgamated Legislative Activities ACWA Statements supporting or Opposing Legislation, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 56)
- ACWA Training Programs, 1975-1977 (Box 72, Folder 57)
- Amalgamated. Training Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 58)
- Amalgamated Training Programs, 1970-1972 (Box 72, Folder 59)
- ACWA - Political Activities, 1950-1975 (Box 72, Folder 60)
- Apparel - Economic Conditions, 1940-1977 (Box 72, Folder 61)
- Men's and Boys' Apparel - Economic Conditions, 1951-1975 (Box 72, Folder 62)
- Tailored Suits, Etc. - Economic Conditions, 1947-1966 (Box 72, Folder 63)
- Wage Payment Systems, 1914-1970 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Wages - General, 1920-1961 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Wage and Price Guidelines, 1966-1979 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Public Works and Economic Development Act of 1965 (See AKA folder for pre-1965 material) (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Service Contract of 1965, 1965-1972 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Planned Mobilization Project, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Procurement Military, 1940-1957 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens Co., 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- ACWA Pay Board Cases - The Enro Shirt Co., Inc., 1972 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- ACWA - Hughes and Hatcher Pay Board Cases, 1972-1973 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- ACWA Pay Board Cases Windbreaker, Inc. + Dau-Jac, Inc. (P-UH), 1972 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- ACWA Pay Board Cases - Jaymar-Ruby, Inc., 1972 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- ACWA Pay Board Cases - The Moyer Company (P-VH), 1972-1973 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Collective Bargaining - Canada, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- ACWA - Education, 1950-1963 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Knit Gloves, 1958-1966 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Apparel Tailored Clothing - Industry Abroad, 1959-1970 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Apparel - Gloves, Dress (Other Than Knit) - Imports, 1950-1974 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Apparel - Gloves, Work - Imports, 1967-1977 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Apparel - Employment, 1950-1973 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Insurance, Health, 1960-1972 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Insurance, Health, 1951-1955 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Insurance, Health, 1938-1949 (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Insurance, Health, 1957-1960 (Box 74, Folder 17)
- Wool and Man-Made Fibers Import Agreements 1971 (Multifiber Arrangement - MFA), 1964-1972 (Box 74, Folder 18)
- U.S. Dept. of Labor - B.L.S.- Productivity Study, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 19)
- Wages Occupational Wage Survey Bushelmen, 1956 (Box 74, Folder 20)
- Wages - Occupational Wage Survey - Neckwear, 1950 (Box 74, Folder 21)
- Wages - Occupational Wage Survey - Work Clothing, 1947-1961 (Box 74, Folder 22)
- Wage Stabilization, 1951-1970 (Box 74, Folder 23)
- Summaries of Testimony and Briefs. Presented to the Apparel Industry Committee Volume II (May), 1939 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Retail Survey, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Survey of ACWA Shops, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Central States - Constitution and By-Laws, 1961-1963 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- ACWA - Actuarial Report - Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan -Valuation Date: Jan 1., 1967 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Retail Division Activity Report, January, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Murray Finley, 1973-1977 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Finley + Sheinkman, 1979-1977 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- All Other, 1973-1977 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Homework in the Glove Industry in New York State, May., 1941 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- ACWA - Wholesale Prices and Price Indexes for Men's Clothing, 1947-1957 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Meeting of Industry Committee No. 2 for the Apparel Industry, Washington. D.C. (June), 1939 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Organizing - Misc., 1963 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Eleven Eleven Corp. Bayamon, P.R., 1964 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Puerto Rico Clothing Co. Las Piedras, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Caribannin, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Central States Trustees Meeting (6th August), 1965 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Overseas Sport Company, Puerto Rico, 1963-1965 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Puerto Rican Clothing Company, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Eleven-Eleven Corp., 1965 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Anasco Sports, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- American Coat and Apron - Schenectady, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Coral Manufacturing - Mayaguez, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Corrozon Knitting Mills, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- Edro Corporation, 1963-1966 (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Women's Bureau Reports - Earnings in selected apparel branches, 1937 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- Revision of Small Business Administration Size Standards, 1954-1967 (Box 76, Folder 15)
- ACWA: Mergers/Acquisitions, 1954-1960 (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Fedl Census - Apparel Survey, 1972-1977 (Box 76, Folder 17)
- Census Bureau - Industry Subcommittees, 1967-1975 (Box 76, Folder 18)
- Fedl Census - Apparel Survey, 1973-1974 (Box 76, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Department Store & Retail Employees Insurance & Pension Funds, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Department Store & Retail Employees - Insurance Fund, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Central States - Questions, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Dallas Meeting, July, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Welfare and Pension Plans Disclosure Act, 1958-1962 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Survey of Wages in the Uniform Clothing Industry, 1938-1940 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions - Apparel Industry, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Hearing Before Sub-Committees of Apparel Industry Committee (House Dresses, Infant's+Children's wear, Robes Uniforms), Washington, D.C, 1939 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- U.S. Wage and hour division - Minimum wage rates - Apparel Industry, 1939 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Hearing Before Sub-Committees of Apparel Industry Committee (Work Clothing, Men's and Boy's Shirts and Blouses, Woven underwear) Washington D.C, 1939 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Meeting and Hearing for the Miscellaneous Apparel Industry, 1941 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Work Book Organizers' Seminar, 1960 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Meeting + Hearing for Single Pants, Shirts, and Allied Garments Industry, 1941 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- Regulations Applicable to Garment Divisions of Apparel Industry, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Average Hourly Earnings in Selected Men's Apparel Industries, 1939 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Mansco, 1966-1967 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Mansco - Manhattan, 1963-1967 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Wilrico, 1961-1967 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rico Clothing Co. General, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Mansco. Reop., 1967-1972 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Central States Joint Board ACWA Insurance Fund, 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Frank Rosenblum - Ohio Retail, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Joe Norban Discount, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- RCIA v ACWA, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- No-Raid Retail Cases - RDIA v ACWA, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Discount Stores Under Contract by Servicing Staff, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Boston Department Store, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Sam's Inc., Detroit, Michigan, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Puerto Rico, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Southern Staff, 1966-1971 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Nirenberg, 1968-1970 (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Department Store and Retail Employees, 1962-1964 (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Central States Joint Board, 1961-1963 (Box 78, Folder 18)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division - Vol.I Supplement to hearing of Apparel Industry Committee, 1939 (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Recommendation of Industry Committee No.2 for Apparel Industry, 1940 (Box 78, Folder 20)
- Minimum Wage Determination for Men's Neckwear Industry, 1950 (Box 78, Folder 21)
- Survey of Wages in Wool Pants Industry (Min Wage), 1941 (Box 78, Folder 22)
- Economic Conditions in the Male Apparel Industry, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Economic Conditions in the Male Apparel Industry, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Trade: Canada: Apparel - ACW/ILG Statements, 1961-1976 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Canadian Clothing Negotiations, Canada., 1970-1973 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Howard Samuel - Speeches and Reports, 1972-1976 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Annual Reports -- Folder 1, 1950-1966 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Annual Reports -- Folder 2, 1967-1981 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Annual Reports -- Folder 3, 1982-1988 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. Government Contract Awards, 1965-1980 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Labor -- General Folder #8, 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Labor -- General Folder #7, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Labor -- General Folder #6, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Labor -- General Folder #5, 1977 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Labor -- General Folder #4, 1975-1976 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Labor -- General Folder #3, 1972-1974 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Labor -- General Folder #2, 1966-1971 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Labor -- General Folder #1, 1948-1965 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Labor -- IUD Org. Material (January), 1968 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Financial and General -- General Folder #6, 1979-1983 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Financial and General -- General Folder #5, 1976-1978 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Financial and General -- General Folder #4, 1968-1975 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Financial and General -- General Folder #3, 1958-1967 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Financial and General -- General Folder #2, 1951-1958 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Financial and General -- General Folder #1 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Boycott Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Boycott Clippings, 1974-1977 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Boycott Materials, 1977-1981 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. "Social Justice" Newsletter, 1976-1980 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. The Stevens Worker, The Stevens Organizer, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (A & M Karagheusian - General Files), 1934-1943 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (A & M Karagheusian - General Files), 1944-1953 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (A & M Karagheusian - General Financial), 1937-1964 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (A & M Karagheusian - Wages), 1942-1947 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (A & M Karagheusian) Aberdeen, N.C., 1957-1978 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (A & M Karagheusian) Albany, GA., 1952-1977 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (A & M Karagheusian) Roselle Park, N.J., 1960-1962 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (A & M Karagheusian) Roselle Park, N.J. (Closed), 1956-1958 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Statesboro, GA. Closing - I - General, 1970-1981 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (A & M Karagheusian) Statesboro, GA, 1961-1975 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (A & M Karagheusian) Freehold, New Jersey, 1950-1966 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Statesboro, GA. Closing - II - Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Statesboro, GA. Closing - III - Analysis, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Utica & Mohawk Cotton Mills (Up to 1952) - Later Files See J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Financial, 1937-1956 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Utica & Mohawk Cotton Mills (Up to 1952) - Later Files See J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Labor, 1937-1952 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Utica Mohawk Plant Clemson, S.C., 1950-1968 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Utica Mohawk Plant Seneca, S.C., 1946-1963 (Box 83, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. United Elastic Corp. Easthampton, Mass. Annual Reports, 1953-1968 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. United Elastic Corp. Easthampton, Mass. (General & Financial), 1937-1986 (Box 83, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. United Elastic Corp. Easthampton, Mass. (General & Labor), 1937-1980 (Box 83, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Easthampton, Mass., 1974-1983 (Box 83, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (West Boylston Plant) Montgomery, Ala. (General & Labor), 1941-1982 (Box 83, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (West Boylston Plant) NLRB Case Montgomery, Ala., 1946-1949 (Box 83, Folder 20)
- A & M Karagheusian, Inc. Wages, 1947-1949 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Abbeville Plant, Abbeville, N.C., 1967 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Allendale Plant, Allendale, S.C., 1966-1984 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Angle Silk Mills, Rocky Mount, Va., 1937-1979 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Apalche Plant Greer (Arlington), S.C., 1938-1981 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Appleton Mill., Anderson, S.C., 1937-1985 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Argon Plant Rockhill, S.C., 1937-1949 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Black Hawk Warehouse Greenville, S.C., 1965-1970 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Lincolnton, N.C. (Boger and Crawford), 1964-1965 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Borden Mills Kingsport, Tenn., 1937-1982 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Bridgetown, Nova Scotia, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Burlington, NC, 1986-1989 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Calhoun Falls, SC, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Carter Fabrics Corp. Greensboro, N.C., 1937-1982 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Carter Fabrics - South Boston, VA, 1939-1965 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Carter Plant Wallace, N.C., 1950-1986 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Delta Finishing Co. Division Philadelphia & Attleboro, Mass., 1943-1954 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Delta #2 Finishing Plant Cheraw, S.C., 1959-1962 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Delta Finishing Plant, Wallace, S.C., 1948-1975 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Drakes Branch, Va., 1987 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Dublin Plant Dublin, G.A., 1946-1986 (Box 84, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Dunean Plant Greenville, S.C., 1932-1975 (Box 84, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Exposition Plant Atlanta, G.A., 1937-1969 (Box 84, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Fayetteville, N.C., 1984 (Box 84, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Franklin, N.H., 1941-1956 (Box 84, Folder 25)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (Gay-Tred Mills) Scottsboro, Ala., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 26)
- J.P. Stevens & Sons Gleasondale, Mass., 1941-1944 (Box 84, Folder 27)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Goldsboro, N.C., 1968-1975 (Box 84, Folder 28)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Greene Plant - Snow Hill, N.C. Formerly: Greene Manufacturing. Co., 1965-1974 (Box 84, Folder 29)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Greer & Victor Plants Greer, S.C., 1938-1982 (Box 84, Folder 30)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Hannah Picket Plant Rockingham, N.C., 1939-1980 (Box 84, Folder 31)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. High Point, N.C., 1979 (Box 84, Folder 32)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Industrial Cotton Mills Div. Rock Hill, S.C., 1937-1982 (Box 84, Folder 33)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Jonesville Mills, Jonesville, S.C., 1951-1981 (Box 84, Folder 34)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Longview Plant Hosiery Div. Longview, N.C., 1965-1989 (Box 84, Folder 35)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Louisville Plant Louisville, Ga., 1960-1986 (Box 84, Folder 36)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Maples Co. (Tufted Rug) Scottsboro, Ala, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 37)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Marland Plant Andover, Mass, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 38)
- J.P. Stevens and Sons Co. Merrimack Wool Mills Div. Dracut, Mass., 1947-1964 (Box 84, Folder 39)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Milledgeville Plant Milledgeville, Ga., 1947-1986 (Box 84, Folder 40)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Nathaniel Plant Dublin Plant, G.A., 1955-1986 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. New Milford, Conn., 1977-1981 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Monaghan Plant Greenville, S.C., 1938-1963 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens and Sons. North Andover, Mass., 1937-1963 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Pamplico Plant. Pamplico, S.C., 1966-1969 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Parker Plant. Greenville, S.C., 1965-1984 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Peace Dale, R.I., 1939-1951 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Pentucket Mill Haverhill, Mass., 1950-1952 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Piedmont Plants (2) Piedmont, S.C., 1932-1980 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Piedmont Manufacturing Co. Piedmont, S.C., 1950 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Greenville, S.C. (Pilot Plant), 1948-1953 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Port Huron, Michigan, 1984-1987 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Ragan Plant. Gastonia, N.C., 1937-1951 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Randleman Plant. Randleman, N.C., 1941-1957 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (Hosiery Division) Redlands, California., 1968 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Republic Cotton Mills. Great Falls, S.C., 1939-1984 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids, N.C. (General), 1950-1980 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Patterson Plant Roanoke Rapids, N.C., 1948-1981 (Box 85, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Roanoke Fabricating Plant. Roanoke Rapids, N.C., 1961 (Box 85, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Roanoke Plants Nos. 1 and 2. Roanoke Rapids, N.C., 1948-1979 (Box 85, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Rosemary Plant. Roanoke Rapids, N.C., 1937-1965 (Box 85, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Rockingham, N.C., 1973 (Box 85, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Martha Baum Div. Rockingham, N.C., 1959-1985 (Box 85, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Rockville, Conn., 1941-1979 (Box 85, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Shelby, N.C., 1969-1981 (Box 85, Folder 25)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Slater Plant. Slater, S.C., 1937-1964 (Box 85, Folder 26)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Taylors Plant. Southern Bleachery & Print Works Taylors, SoC. (formerly Burlington Industries), 1939-1982 (Box 85, Folder 27)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Stanley, N.C., 1975 (Box 85, Folder 28)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (Stevecoknit, Inc., subs.), 1966-1985 (Box 85, Folder 29)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Tifton Plant. Tifton, GA., 1957-1986 (Box 85, Folder 30)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Turnersburg Plant. Turnersburg, N.C., 1963-1972 (Box 85, Folder 31)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (United Elastic Div.) Stuart, Va., 1980-1986 (Box 85, Folder 32)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. (United Elastic Co. Div.) West Haven, Conn., 1970-1973 (Box 85, Folder 33)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Wagram, N.C., 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 34)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Walterboro Plant. Walterboro, S.C., 1966-1990 (Box 85, Folder 35)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Watts Mills Laurens, S.C., 1937-1979 (Box 85, Folder 36)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Montgomery, Ala. See: West Boylston Plant (Box 85, Folder 37)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. White Horse Mills (Formerly Maverick) Greenville, S.C., 1963-1976 (Box 85, Folder 38)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Whitmire Plant. Whitmire, S.C., 1937-1985 (Box 85, Folder 39)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Woolwine, Virginia, 1979-1990 (Box 85, Folder 40)
- Reports on Matters relating to Army Contracts, 1958 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Minimum Wage - Men's and Boys' Shirts (except Work Shirts) and Nightwear, 1956 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Minimum Wage - Footwear, Processed Waste, Wooden Containers, Work Shirts, 1955-1956 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Minimum Wage - Processed Waste, Work Shirts, 1957 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Wage and Hour division - Miscellaneous Apparel Industry, 1941 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Hours and Earnings in Certain Men's-Wear Industries - Knit Underwear, Woven Cotton Underwear, Work Clothing, Work Shirts, Dress Shirts, 1938 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Hours and Earnings in Certain Men's-Wear Industries - Caps and Cloth Hats, Neckwear, Work and Knit Gloves, Handkerchiefs, 1939 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Hours and Earnings in Certain Men's-Wear Industries - Raincoats, Sport Jackets, 1940 (Box 86, Folder 8)